[
    
    {
        "QorL":"Q",
        "question":"The visible characters in an organisms is known as",
        "options":
        [
            "Prototype",
            "Stereotype",
            "Phenotype",
            "Genotype"
        ],
        "correctAns": "Phenotype"
    },
    {
        "QorL":"Q",
        "question":"The human species has genetics roots in",
        "options":
        [
            "America",
            "Africa",
            "Australia",
            "Antarctica"
        ],
        "correctAns": "Africa"
    },
    {
        "QorL":"Q",
        "question":"According to scientists, aves have evolved from",
        "options":
        [
            "Mammals",
            "Amphibians",
            "Reptiles",
            "Arthropods"
        ],
        "correctAns": "Reptiles"
    },
    {
        "QorL":"Q",
        "question":"One of the following traits cannot be inherited. This one is",
        "options":
        [
            "Colour of eyes",
            "Colour of skin",
            "Size of body",
            "Nature of colour"
        ],
        "correctAns": "Size of body"
    },
    {
        "QorL":"Q",
        "question":"Carbon dating method is based upon the radioactive decay of naturally occurring",
        "options":
        [
            "C- 17",
            "C- 14",
            "Nitrogen",
            "Hydrogen"
        ],
        "correctAns": "C- 14"
    },
    {
        "QorL":"Q",
        "question":"Paleontological Evidences include",
        "options":
        [
            "Fossil",
            "Sculpture",
            "Civilizations",
            "None of these"
        ],
        "correctAns": "Fossil"
    },
    {
        "QorL":"Q",
        "question":"Darwin had published a book titled",
        "options":
        [
            "Origin of species",
            "Natural species",
            "Synthetic selection",
            "All of the above"
        ],
        "correctAns": "Origin of species"
    },
    {
        "QorL":"Q",
        "question":"Willard Libby has been awarded with Nobel Prize",
        "options":
        [
            "1980",
            "1970",
            "1950",
            "1960"
        ],
        "correctAns": "1960"
    },
    {
        "QorL":"Q",
        "question":"Vestigial organs",
        "options":
        [
            "Appendix",
            "Body hairs",
            "Tail bone",
            "All the above"
        ],
        "correctAns": "All the above"
    },
    {
        "QorL":"Q",
        "question":"Formation of new species of plants and animals is the effect of evolution",
        "options":
        [
            "Evolution",
            "Variation",
            "Speciation",
            "None of the above"
        ],
        "correctAns": "Speciation"
    }
]